webassist.com 2009-09-27

# WebAssist - Privacy Policy

### Effective Date: March 8, 2006

WebAssist.com Corporation. ("WebAssist") values the users of our web site (the "Web Site") and the services offered on it (the "WebAssist Services"). We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of your personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we may collect when you use the Web Site and the WebAssist Services. Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you of the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. By using the WebAssist Web Site you are accepting the practices described in this policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: privacy@webassist.com   

### Does WebAssist Ever Make Changes to its Privacy Policy?

We may make changes to the Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by sending an email to the address you have provided, posting the updated version of the Privacy Policy on the Web Site, or, through the use of cookies, informing you when you first sign on to the Web Site after we have made changes. If you receive notification of a change in our Privacy Policy, you must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures. You may not be able to receive notices from us if your cookies are not set to accept. Your continued use of the Web Site will be subject to the then-current privacy policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. 

### What Types of Information Does WebAssist Collect From Me?

**Personal Information.** We collect Personal Information from you. As explained above, Personal Information is information that can be used to identify you individually, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, and email address. 

**Non-Personal Information.** We also collect "non-personal" information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous web site you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your IP Address. This information ("Non-Personal Information") cannot be easily used to personally identify you. 

### How and When Does WebAssist Collect This Information?

**Providing Information to Us.** We collect Personal Information from you when you provide it to us. For example, if you purchase a product sold through the Web Site, we may collect your name, mailing address, telephone number, and email address. If you sign up to receive a newsletter, we will collect your email address. 

**Communications With Us.** If you communicate with us regarding the Web Site or the WebAssist Services, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication, except credit card information. 

**Analytic and Reporting Technologies.** Like the operators of most web sites, we use analytic and reporting technologies to record Non-Personal Information such as Internet domain and host names, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser software and operating system types, clickstream patterns, and the dates and times that the Web Site and the WebAssist Services are accessed. 

### How Does WebAssist Use My Information?

**Personal Information.** We use Personal Information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the WebAssist Services and the Web Site, fulfilling requests for information, producing and shipping the products that you order, customer support, and to send you promotional information. For example, if you create an Affiliate Account, we will use the information that you provide to communicate with you and pay you any commissions that you earn. Similarly, if you sign up to receive a WebAssist newsletter, we will use the email address you provide to send you the newsletters. 

**Non-Personal Information.** We use non-personal information to track your use of the Web Site and the WebAssist Services and for other internal purposes, particularly providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving the WebAssist Services and the Web Site. 

### How Does WebAssist Use My Information?

Generally speaking, we do not intentionally disclose your information to third parties without your consent. However we reserve the right to do so because it is necessary to the operation and continued growth of our business or to protect the rights of others. These instances are discussed below: 

**Disclosure to Successors.** We may disclose your Personal Information to any successor-in-interest of ours, such as a company that acquires us. In the event WebAssist goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. In the event of a change in ownership or control of your personal information, we will send a notice by email to the address that you have provided and/or post a notice on our Web Site of any such change. 

**Disclosure to Unaffiliated Third Parties.** We may disclose your Personal Information to prevent an emergency, to protect or enforce our rights, to protect or enforce the rights of a third party, or as required or permitted by law (including, without limitation, to comply with a subpoena or court order). In particular, if you are an Affiliate, we may disclose your information to a third party that alleges that you have infringed their intellectual property rights. Similarly, if you allege that an Affiliate allegedly infringes your intellectual property rights, we may disclose your information to that Affiliate. 

**Disclosure to Third-Party Service Providers.** We may contract with various third parties who help us provide and maintain the Web Site or the WebAssist Services. For example, we use a third-party to process payments made to us, and may subcontract out production, fulfillment, or other operations. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your Personal Information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question. We cannot guarantee that such third parties will not disclose your Personal Information. 

**Disclosure of Non-Personal Information.** We will disclose Non-Personal Information, in aggregate form, to potential strategic partners, advertisers, investors, customers, and others. You may not "opt out" of the sharing of this information. However, it cannot be easily used to identify you personally. 

**Opt In Use and Disclosure.** Users of the Web Site will have opportunities to opt-in to have their information used for other purposes. If you do not wish your information shared, it can be prevented by not opting-in for the particular purpose or promotion. 

### How Does WebAssist Use My Information?

A cookie is a message that is sent to your computer from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Most web sites use cookies. We use cookies to track your use of the Web Site and the WebAssist Services, provide you with a more personalized user experience, and to allow you to sign in and begin use of the WebAssist Services automatically when you visit the Web Site. We may also use cookies to ensure that you have been notified of and agreed to the then-current version of the Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, and any other agreements and policies relating to your use of the Web Site or the WebAssist Services. Cookies used by WebAssist are not linked to Personal Information. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by WebAssist only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

### Does WebAssist Protect My Personal Information?

**Personal Information.** Whenever we obtain your Personal Information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we are not insurers of the security of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control. 

**Web Site Content.** The content that you store, post, or transmit on or through the Web Site, except for submissions to the Premium Support Service, may be accessed by other users, including people that you do not know. We are not responsible for the actions of others. Therefore, you should use care in communicating with other users and only disclose your Personal Information to other users that you know to be trustworthy. You should not assume that your content will be kept private. 

### How Can I Review and Make Changes to My Personal Information?

You can obtain a copy of and request that we correct errors in your Personal Information by emailing us at privacy@WebAssist.com. For your protection, you will be required to provide proof of your identity to obtain a copy of your Personal Information. If your Personal Information changes or if you no longer want to use the WebAssist Services, you may correct, update or deactivate your Personal Information and/or your account through your account management screen. If you would like to deactivate or terminate your account you can also contact Customer Service. 

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

### Does This Privacy Policy Apply When I Access Third Party Web Sites?

You may be able to access third-party web sites directly from the Web Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access such web sites. We cannot control how third parties may use Personal Information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third-party web site you visit before using it or disclosing your Personal Information to its provider. 

### What About Children's Privacy?

**Under Thirteen.** The WebAssist Services are intended for users ages 13 and older. Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect or use any Personal Information from children that we know to be under the age of 13. In addition, we will delete any information in our database that we know originates from a child under the age of 13. 

**Thirteen to Seventeen.** Prospective users between the ages of 13 and 17 can only use the WebAssist Services under their parents' or legal guardian's supervision. If you are between the ages of 13 and 17, you, your parent, or your legal guardian may request that we delete any of your Personal Information in our database and/or opt-out from receiving communications from us. If you wish to do so, please contact us at the email address provided below. 

### Can I "Opt Out" From Receiving Communications From WebAssist?

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at privacy@WebAssist.com. We also offer you an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications through your account management screen. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact WebAssist by e-mailing privacy@WebAssist.com or my mail at 8899 University Center Ln, Ste 330, San Diego, CA 92122.
